{
  "config_1": {
    "0,0": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "otn_01",
      "back": "otn_02"
    },
    "1,0": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "otn_02",
      "back": "otn_03"
    },
    "2,0": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "otn_03",
      "back": "oto_01"
    },
    "3,0": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "oto_01",
      "back": "oto_02"
    },
    "0,1": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_02",
      "back": "oto_03"
    },
    "1,1": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_03",
      "back": "oto_04"
    },
    "2,1": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_04",
      "back": "oto_05"
    },
    "3,1": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_05",
      "back": "otoa_01"
    },
    "0,2": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otoa_01",
      "back": "otoa_02"
    },
    "1,2": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otoa_02",
      "back": "otoa_03"
    },
    "2,2": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otoa_03",
      "back": "otw_01"
    },
    "3,2": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otw_01",
      "back": "otw_02"
    },
    "0,3": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "otw_02",
      "back": "otw_03"
    },
    "1,3": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "otw_03",
      "back": "oth_01"
    },
    "2,3": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_01",
      "back": "oth_02"
    },
    "3,3": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_02",
      "back": "oth_03"
    },
    "0,4": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "oth_03",
      "back": "otn_01"
    },
    "1,4": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "otn_01",
      "back": "oto_02"
    },
    "2,4": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "oto_03",
      "back": "otoa_02"
    },
    "3,4": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "otw_01",
      "back": "oth_01"
    }
  },
  "config_2": {
    "0,0": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "otn_02",
      "back": "otn_03"
    },
    "1,0": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "otn_03",
      "back": "oto_01"
    },
    "2,0": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "oto_01",
      "back": "oto_02"
    },
    "3,0": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "oto_02",
      "back": "oto_03"
    },
    "0,1": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_03",
      "back": "oto_04"
    },
    "1,1": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_04",
      "back": "oto_05"
    },
    "2,1": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_05",
      "back": "otoa_01"
    },
    "3,1": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "otoa_01",
      "back": "otoa_02"
    },
    "0,2": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otoa_02",
      "back": "otoa_03"
    },
    "1,2": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otoa_03",
      "back": "otw_01"
    },
    "2,2": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otw_01",
      "back": "otw_02"
    },
    "3,2": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otw_02",
      "back": "otw_03"
    },
    "0,3": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "otw_03",
      "back": "oth_01"
    },
    "1,3": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_01",
      "back": "oth_02"
    },
    "2,3": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_02",
      "back": "oth_03"
    },
    "3,3": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_03",
      "back": "otn_02"
    },
    "0,4": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "otn_02",
      "back": "oto_03"
    },
    "1,4": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "oto_04",
      "back": "otoa_02"
    },
    "2,4": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "otw_02",
      "back": "oth_01"
    },
    "3,4": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "oth_03",
      "back": "otoa_03"
    }
  },
  "config_3": {
    "0,0": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "otn_03",
      "back": "oto_01"
    },
    "1,0": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "oto_01",
      "back": "oto_02"
    },
    "2,0": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "oto_02",
      "back": "oto_03"
    },
    "3,0": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 0,
      "front": "oto_03",
      "back": "oto_04"
    },
    "0,1": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_04",
      "back": "oto_05"
    },
    "1,1": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "oto_05",
      "back": "otoa_01"
    },
    "2,1": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "otoa_01",
      "back": "otoa_02"
    },
    "3,1": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 1,
      "front": "otoa_02",
      "back": "otoa_03"
    },
    "0,2": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otoa_03",
      "back": "otw_01"
    },
    "1,2": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otw_01",
      "back": "otw_02"
    },
    "2,2": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otw_02",
      "back": "otw_03"
    },
    "3,2": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 2,
      "front": "otw_03",
      "back": "oth_01"
    },
    "0,3": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_01",
      "back": "oth_02"
    },
    "1,3": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_02",
      "back": "oth_03"
    },
    "2,3": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "oth_03",
      "back": "otn_01"
    },
    "3,3": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 3,
      "front": "otn_01",
      "back": "oto_02"
    },
    "0,4": {
      "column": 0,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "oto_03",
      "back": "otoa_02"
    },
    "1,4": {
      "column": 1,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "otw_02",
      "back": "oth_01"
    },
    "2,4": {
      "column": 2,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "oth_03",
      "back": "otoa_01"
    },
    "3,4": {
      "column": 3,
      "row": 4,
      "front": "otw_01",
      "back": "otn_02"
    }
  }
}